{
  "medium": [
    {
      "question_number": 1,
      "question": "Who did Manchester United beat in the Quarter-Final on their way to winning the Champions League in 1999?",
      "option_a": "Borussia Dortmund",
      "option_b": "Valencia",
      "option_c": "Inter Milan",
      "option_d": "Dynamo Kiev",
      "correct": "Inter Milan"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 2,
      "question": "When did Manchester United first win the FA Cup?",
      "option_a": 1909,
      "option_b": 1928,
      "option_c": 1912,
      "option_d": 1935,
      "correct": 1909
    },
    {
      "question_number": 3,
      "question": "What club did Manchester United sign Ruud Van Nistelrooy from?",
      "option_a": "Ajax",
      "option_b": "Feyenoord",
      "option_c": "PSV Eindhoven",
      "option_d": "FC Twente",
      "correct": "PSV Eindhoven"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 4,
      "question": "Which team did Manchester United beat to win the 1991 Cup Winners Cup?",
      "option_a": "AC Milan",
      "option_b": "Paris St Germain",
      "option_c": "Porto",
      "option_d": "Barcelona",
      "correct": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 5,
      "question": "United had gone 40 years without defeat in European competition at home but their run was ended in the 1996-97 tournament. Which team ended that run?",
      "option_a": "Dynamo Kiev",
      "option_b": "Sporting Lisbon",
      "option_c": "Deportivo La Coruna",
      "option_d": "Fenerbache",
      "correct": "Fenerbache"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 6,
      "question": "Where did United sign Steve Bruce from?",
      "option_a": "Norwich City",
      "option_b": "Aston Villa",
      "option_c": "Birmingham City",
      "option_d": "Hull City",
      "correct": "Norwich City"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 7,
      "question": "Who was the first Manchester United captain from outside the United Kingdom or the Republic of Ireland?",
      "option_a": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_b": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_c": "Nemanja Vidic",
      "option_d": "Dwight Yorke",
      "correct": "Eric Cantona"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 8,
      "question": "Who became Manchester United's Record signing in 2002?",
      "option_a": "Juan Sebastian Veron",
      "option_b": "Rio Ferdinand",
      "option_c": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_d": "Wayne Rooney",
      "correct": "Rio Ferdinand"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 9,
      "question": "From which of these clubs was Ole Gunnar Solskjaer signed?",
      "option_a": "FK Brann",
      "option_b": "Valaerenga",
      "option_c": "Lillestrom",
      "option_d": "Molde",
      "correct": "Molde"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 10,
      "question": "Which team did Brian McClair join Manchester United from?",
      "option_a": "Cork City",
      "option_b": "Celtic",
      "option_c": "Aberdeen",
      "option_d": "Cardiff City",
      "correct": "Celtic"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 11,
      "question": "Against which team did Dwight Yorke open up his Manchester United account?",
      "option_a": "Charlton Athletic",
      "option_b": "West Ham",
      "option_c": "Derby County",
      "option_d": "Everton",
      "correct": "Charlton Athletic"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 12,
      "question": "From what club did Manchester United sign Andrei Kanchelskis?",
      "option_a": "Fiorentina",
      "option_b": "Saturn Moscow Oblast",
      "option_c": "Dyanmo Kiev",
      "option_d": "Shakhtar Donetsk",
      "correct": "Shakhtar Donetsk"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 13,
      "question": "After drawing the first leg 1-1, United beat Juventus in a thrilling second leg 3-2 to reach the 1999 Champions League final. Who scored the winner?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Andy Cole",
      "option_d": "Roy Keane",
      "correct": "Andy Cole"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 14,
      "question": "Manchester United have won the UEFA Super Cup just once. In what year did they win it and who did they beat?",
      "option_a": "Lazio in 1999",
      "option_b": "Zenit St Petersburg in 2008",
      "option_c": "Real Madrid in 2017",
      "option_d": "Red Star Belgrade in 1991",
      "correct": "Red Star Belgrade in 1991"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 15,
      "question": "How many times in United's history have they been relegated?",
      "option_a": 0,
      "option_b": 5,
      "option_c": 3,
      "option_d": 9,
      "correct": 5
    },
    {
      "question_number": 16,
      "question": "In the 1998-99 Champions League Final v Bayern Munich, Solskjaer and Sheringham (who came on as substitutes) scored the dramatic goals in the last minute of the game, and then in injury time, to give United a 2-1 win. Which two players were replaced by Solskjaer and Sheringam?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes & Roy Keane",
      "option_b": "Nicky Butt & Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Jesper Blomqvist & Andy Cole",
      "option_d": "David Beckham & Dwight Yorke",
      "correct": "Jesper Blomqvist & Andy Cole"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 17,
      "question": "When Andy Cole signed from Newcastle United, who went the other way as part of the deal?",
      "option_a": "Robbie Savage",
      "option_b": "Dion Dublin",
      "option_c": "Paul McGrath",
      "option_d": "Keith Gillespie",
      "correct": "Keith Gillespie"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 18,
      "question": "Who scored the winning goal in the 1990 F.A. Cup final?",
      "option_a": "Brian McClair",
      "option_b": "Lee Martin",
      "option_c": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Gary Pallister",
      "correct": "Lee Martin"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 19,
      "question": "Shinji Kagawa scored his first and only Manchester United hat-trick against which club?",
      "option_a": "Norwich City",
      "option_b": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_c": "Everton",
      "option_d": "Portsmouth",
      "correct": "Norwich City"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 20,
      "question": "Diego Forlan scored his first United goal against which club?",
      "option_a": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_b": "Maccabi Haifa",
      "option_c": "Aston Villa",
      "option_d": "Panathinaikos",
      "correct": "Maccabi Haifa"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 21,
      "question": "Teddy Sheringham made 149 appearances in a United shirt. How many goals did he score?",
      "option_a": 56,
      "option_b": 86,
      "option_c": 46,
      "option_d": 66,
      "correct": 46
    },
    {
      "question_number": 22,
      "question": "Which of these United players retired with 129 caps for their country?",
      "option_a": "David Beckham",
      "option_b": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_c": "Edwin Van Der Saar",
      "option_d": "Wayne Rooney",
      "correct": "Peter Schmeichel"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 23,
      "question": "In the 1985 FA Cup Semi-Final replay Manchester United defeated Liverpool 2-1. Which two players scored United's goals?",
      "option_a": "Gordon Strachen & Paul McGrath",
      "option_b": "Frank Stapleton & Norman Whiteside",
      "option_c": "Mark Hughes & Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Graeme Hogg & Norman Whiteside",
      "correct": "Mark Hughes & Bryan Robson"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 24,
      "question": "Which of these players has the most appearances for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_b": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_c": "Gary Neville",
      "option_d": "Bill Foulkes",
      "correct": "Ryan Giggs"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 25,
      "question": "Wayne Rooney scored how many goals in europe for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": 34,
      "option_b": 36,
      "option_c": 39,
      "option_d": 45,
      "correct": 39
    },
    {
      "question_number": 26,
      "question": "How many Manchester United players have won the Ballon d'Or whilst wearing the United shirt?",
      "option_a": 2,
      "option_b": 6,
      "option_c": 4,
      "option_d": 8,
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "question_number": 27,
      "question": "Wayne Rooney scored 10 of his 34 goals in the Champions League against two Italian teams. Who were they?",
      "option_a": "Roma & AC Milan",
      "option_b": "Inter Milan & Juventus",
      "option_c": "Roma & Inter Milan",
      "option_d": "AC Milan & Inter Milan",
      "correct": "Roma & AC Milan"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 28,
      "question": "How many goals did United score on the way to winning the 1999 Champions League?",
      "option_a": 20,
      "option_b": 25,
      "option_c": 29,
      "option_d": 36,
      "correct": 29
    },
    {
      "question_number": 29,
      "question": "How many goals did United score on their way to winning the 2008 Champions League final?",
      "option_a": 13,
      "option_b": 20,
      "option_c": 24,
      "option_d": 18,
      "correct": 20
    },
    {
      "question_number": 30,
      "question": "Who holds the record for most goals scored in all competitions in one season for United?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_b": "Denis Law",
      "option_c": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_d": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "correct": "Denis Law"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 31,
      "question": "Cristiano Ronaldo is the most recent player to win the Ballon D'Or in a United shirt. Who was the last person before him?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_b": "George Best",
      "option_c": "David Beckham",
      "option_d": "Denis Law",
      "correct": "George Best"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 32,
      "question": "George Best shares the record for most goals scored in one game for United with 6. Who does he share it with?",
      "option_a": "Harold Halse",
      "option_b": "Dimitar Berbatov",
      "option_c": "Andy Cole",
      "option_d": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "correct": "Harold Halse"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 33,
      "question": "How many Champions League goals did David Beckham score for United?",
      "option_a": 15,
      "option_b": 10,
      "option_c": 20,
      "option_d": 5,
      "correct": 15
    },
    {
      "question_number": 34,
      "question": "Manchester United beat Real Madrid on the way to winning the 1968 European Cup. What was the score in the away leg?",
      "option_a": "2-1",
      "option_b": "3-3",
      "option_c": "1-0",
      "option_d": "4-1",
      "correct": "3-3"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 35,
      "question": "Dwight Yorke led United's goalscoring charge in the league in the 1998-99 season. How many goals did he score that season?",
      "option_a": 17,
      "option_b": 18,
      "option_c": 19,
      "option_d": 20,
      "correct": 18
    },
    {
      "question_number": 36,
      "question": "Who scored the only goal as United beat Palmeiras 1-0 to win the 1999 Intercontinental Cup?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_d": "Roy Keane",
      "correct": "Roy Keane"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 37,
      "question": "United beat which Ecuadorian team 1-0 to win the FIFA Club World Cup in 2008",
      "option_a": "LDU Quito",
      "option_b": "Aucas",
      "option_c": "Olmedo",
      "option_d": "Guayaquil City",
      "correct": "LDU Quito"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 38,
      "question": "Against which team did Wayne Rooney score his 100th goal for United?",
      "option_a": "Wigan Athletic",
      "option_b": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_c": "Portsmouth",
      "option_d": "Birmingham City",
      "correct": "Wigan Athletic"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 39,
      "question": "Against which team did Ole Gunnar Solskjaer score his 100th goal for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Zalaegerzeg",
      "option_b": "Maccabi Haifa",
      "option_c": "West Brom",
      "option_d": "Leeds United",
      "correct": "West Brom"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 40,
      "question": "Who is the youngest player to make an appearance for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Angel Gomes",
      "option_b": "Duncan Edwards",
      "option_c": "David Gaskell",
      "option_d": "Norman Whiteside",
      "correct": "David Gaskell"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 41,
      "question": "Who is United's top foreign record goalscorer?",
      "option_a": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_b": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_c": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option_d": "Dwight Yorke",
      "correct": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 42,
      "question": "How many goals did Diego Forlan score for United?",
      "option_a": 20,
      "option_b": 17,
      "option_c": 25,
      "option_d": 12,
      "correct": 17
    },
    {
      "question_number": 43,
      "question": "Manchester United signed Bryan Robson from which club?",
      "option_a": "West Brom",
      "option_b": "Birmingham City",
      "option_c": "Aston Villa",
      "option_d": "Wolves",
      "correct": "West Brom"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 44,
      "question": "How many goals did Bryan Robson score for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": 95,
      "option_b": 100,
      "option_c": 99,
      "option_d": 82,
      "correct": 99
    },
    {
      "question_number": 45,
      "question": "Which goalkeeper holds the record for most clean sheets at United?",
      "option_a": "Alex Stepney",
      "option_b": "Gary Bailey",
      "option_c": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_d": "Edwin Van Der Sar",
      "correct": "Peter Schmeichel"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 46,
      "question": "Alex Büttner scored on his debut against which club?",
      "option_a": "Bolton Wanderers",
      "option_b": "West Brom",
      "option_c": "Wigan Athletic",
      "option_d": "Chelsea",
      "correct": "Wigan Athletic"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 47,
      "question": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer scored two goals as United won the Champions league in 1999. One against Bayern Munich and the other against _____?",
      "option_a": "Barcelona",
      "option_b": "Juventus",
      "option_c": "Brondby",
      "option_d": "Inter Milan",
      "correct": "Brondby"
    },
    {
      "question_number": 48,
      "question": "Marcus Rashford scored two goals on his United debut. Who provided the assist for the 2nd goal?",
      "option_a": "Guillermo Varela",
      "option_b": "Juan Mata",
      "option_c": "Jesse Lingard",
      "option_d": "Joe Riley",
      "correct": "Guillermo Varela"
    }
  ]
}
